Barbara: Now, let’s go upstairs.
Follow me. Be careful. The ceiling is very low here.
Leo: It’s a very old house.
Barbara: Yes, the house is three hundred years old.
My family lived here for nearly eighty years.
There are six bedrooms. This was my father’s bedroom.
Kim: Is there central heating in the house?
Barbara: Yes, there is. Why do you ask?
Are you cold?
Kim: Yes, it’s very cold in here.
Leo: That’s because we’re from California.
Barbara: Let’s go and see the other bedrooms.
Leo: Yes, of course.
Well, what do you think, Kim? I love it! Don’t you?
Kim: I’m not sure. There’s something about the house I don’t like.
Leo: Kim, it’s perfect for the kids. Think of the garden.
And it’s a real authentic English country house. What do you say?
Kim: I suppose so. If you’re sure.
Leo: I am sure! Miss…er, Barbara.
We want it. We want to rent the house.
Barbara: Excellent.
Leo: When can we move in?
Barbara: As soon as you like.